你正被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密的系统
The government has a secret system-
有一台机器 无时无刻不在监视着你
A machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
我知道 因为这个系统是我建的
I know,because I built it.
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动 但事实上它可以侦测到任何事
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror,but it sees everything...
包括发生在平民百姓身上的暴力犯罪 像你一样的普通百姓
Violent crimes involving ordinary people,people like you,
在政府看来无关紧要的暴力犯罪
crimes the government considered irrelevant.
他们不采取行动  所以我决定我要去干预
They wouldn't act,so I decided I would.
但我需要一个搭档 某个有能力去干预的人
But I needed a partner - Someone with the skills to intervene.
为了躲避当局追查  我们只能秘密行动
Hunted by the authorities,we work in secret.
你永远不会发现我们
You will never find us.
但受害者 罪犯 要是你的号码 被选出来 我们一定会找到你
But victim or perpetrator,if your number's up,we'll find you.
疑犯追踪 第1季 第9集
Person of Interest S01E09 720p HDTV x264
他归你了
He's all yours.
我已经告诉过你们美国人了... 我运送的是蔬果
I already told the other americans... I deliver fruits and vegetables.
你为基地组织运送炸药
You deliver explosives for al-qaeda.
你的电话引爆了自杀式炸弹 杀死了三名在费卢杰的美国士兵
Your cell is responsible for a suicide bomb that killed three u.s.Soldiers in fallujah.
你应该告诉我其余炸弹的位置
You should tell me the location of the remainder of those explosives.
跟我说吧 不然你得去跟我老大谈谈了
Talk to me,or else you're gonna have to talk to my boss.
相信我 你绝不会想跟我老大谈话的
And believe me when I tell you,you don't want to talk to my boss.
好吧
All right.
你好 Yusuf
Hello,yusuf.
靠太近了 已经够了 她得除掉... 就今天
Getting too close - Enough already.She goes... Today.
一定要做得干干净净
But it's got to be clean.
你不能一直这个样子来这儿 我要走了
- You can't keep coming in here like this. - I gotta go.
Carter警探 Kovach太太来保释她的丈夫
Detective carter? It's Mrs.Kovach here to bail out her husband.
- 又来了? - 我想也许你能和她谈谈
- Again? - Figured maybe you could talk to her.
谢谢
Thanks.
我负责的是凶杀案 Kovach太太 明白么?
I work homicide,mrs.Kovach,okay?
等你丈夫最终把你打死时 负责调查的就是我
I'm the one who has to investigate it when your husband finally beats you to death.
你一次次地跟我们说是意外
Look,every time you tell us it was an accident,
每说一次 你笨拙 经常出事故的形象就加深一点
you're strengthening the story he's gonna use to get out of it-
而他将会用这一点来逃避惩罚
That you were clumsy,accident-prone.
你听到我说话了么?
Do you hear me?
是楼梯 我从楼梯上摔下来了
The stairs. I fell down the stairs.
如果他再碰你 打给我
If he puts his hands on you again,call me.
抱歉 我得走了
Sorry. I have to go.
我不知道你为什么要烦心 Carter 你救不了所有人
I don't know why you bother,carter.You can't save 'em all.
这是一起潜在的凶杀案
That's a homicide waiting to happen.
我只是想有点改变 看能不能阻止
Figured I'd try to stop one for a change.
几个星期前 你开枪打伤那家伙的DNA报告出来了
Dna came back on the shooter you winged a couple weeks ago.
那个对你开枪的家伙
The guy who took a shot at you.
有一半的DNA与Marlene Elias匹配
Half the dna matched marlene elias...
另一半与Don Moretti匹配
The other half... Don moretti.
Carl Elias 那个你在40年前杀了他的母亲
Carl elias-the bastard son you left to rot in the system
你的情妇后 扔在领养系统里自生自灭的
after you murdered his mother almost 40 years ago.
- 你的私生子 - 我之前就说过 亲爱的
- Your mistress. - I told you before,sweetheart.
我不是那谁谁谁的父亲
I ain't the father of nobody by that name.
DNA可不这么说 Don 你们的DNA完全匹配
Dna says otherwise,don.You're a perfect match.
你猜怎么着 你的儿子现在长大了
And guess what.Your son's all grown up now.
这是一些他最近的受害者
Just a few of his recent victims.
退休的警探Bernie Sullivan 你以前的分舵老大Vincent Deluca
Retired detective bernie sullivan,your old capo vincent deluca.
这算什么? 关我什么事? 我反正是要老死在这里了
What is this? What do I care? I'm gonna die an old man in here.
或许你会比你预想的要早死
Maybe sooner than you think.
你杀了他的母亲 你把他丢在狼窝里
You killed his mother,and you left him to the wolves.
你觉得他会怎么对你?
What do you think he's gonna do to you?
是我可不会指望有父亲节的卡片
I wouldn't expect any father's day cards.
如果你帮了我  我能给你提供保护
If you help me,I can offer you protective custody.
你以为你在跟谁讲话?
Who do you think you're talking to?
你不明白 无论在哪里 Elias都能接近你
You don't get it. Elias can get to you anywhere.
他能找到你认识的人 通过他们接近你
He can find someone you know,turn them on you.
这不是能不能的问题 而是时间问题
And you know what?It's not a question of if,but when.
这家伙已经干掉了一个警察 因为你查这案子靠得太近 就要杀你
Telling me this guy already took out a cop,took a shot at you 'cause you got too close,
你却跑来这儿警告我?
and you came here to warn me,huh?
你就当成是礼节性拜访吧
Consider it a courtesy call.
是有个专案组在查Elias 还是只有你一个人在查 警探?
There a task force going after this elias,or is it just you,detective?
这是什么意思?
What is that supposed to mean?
从我的角度看 你是孤身一人
Way it looks from my side of the fence,you're all alone.
我觉得也许他正想要干掉你呢
Sounds to me like maybe he's coming after you.
所有人员注意 168街和奥杜邦交界发生枪击案
All units respond - Shooting at 168th and audubon.
我一听到通知就赶来了
I came as soon as I heard the description.
一个年轻的非裔美国男性 在回家的途中被射死
Yeah,got a young african-american male gunned down on his way home.
路边到处是9毫米弹壳
I got 9-millimeter casings all over the curb.
看起来像驾车枪击
Looks like it was a drive-by.
有目击者看到那辆车了吗?
Any witnesses see the car?
在这个街区? 你在开玩笑吧?
In this neighborhood? You're kidding,right?
- Ronnie Middleton - 你认识这个孩子?
- Ronnie middleton. - You knew this kid?
他是六个月前 发生在布朗克斯的枪击案的目击证人
He witnessed a shooting six months ago up in the bronx.
指证了杀手的身份 是这个街区的暴徒Hector Alvarez
I.d.'d the shooter-neighborhood thug hector alvarez.
- 这孩子告了密? - 是的 但他临阵退缩了
- This kid was a snitch? - Yeah.He got cold feet though.
撤回了他的证词 检察官就撤诉了
Recanted his testimony. D.a. Dropped the case.
看起来Hector找到了他
Looks like hector found him.
他这次溜不掉了
He won't get away with it again.
Ronnie的随身物品呢?
Was ronnie carrying?
只有一个手机 一个苏打水瓶
Yeah,just a,uh,cell phone,and that soda bottle.
Mariquitas可乐?
Mariquitas cola?
墨西哥的苏打水
Mexican soda.
这不是哪里都有卖的
They don't sell that everywhere.
我知道有一个地方卖这个
I think I know a place that does.
我知道有人看到了些什么
And I know somebody saw something.
让他们开口又是另外一回事了
Yeah,getting them to talk is another matter.
我很肯定你有魅力让他们开口的 Fusco
I'm sure you'll charm something out of them,fusco.
Carter 我们一起工作有段时间了
You know,carter,we've been working together for a while now.
我的朋友都叫我"Lionel"
My friends call me "lionel."
你有名字吗?
You got a first name?
当然 "警探"
Sure."detective."
我是纽约警署的Fusco警探
My name's detective fusco with the n.y.p.d.
如果有人看到或听到什么 跟今晚发生的案子有关的事情
If anyone has seen or heard anything pertaining to what hpened here tonight,
你们可以打给我
you can call me at-
我已经有你的名片了 Lionel
I already have your card,lionel.
- 你在这来干什么? - 就是随便看看
- What the hell are you doing here? - Just checking in.
发生什么事情了?
What happened here?
有人中弹了  这街区常常发生这事
Lead poisoning.It's going around the neighborhood.
纽约警署 您是...?
N.y.p.d.,mister...?
Castillo 我要打烊了
Castillo.I'm-i'm closed for the night.
你今天晚上 有看到什么吗 Castillo先生?
You see what happened out here tonight,Mr.Castillo?
我在后面忙活着 直到警察来之前我什么都没有听到
I was busy in the back.I- I-I didn't hear anything till the police showed up.
我觉得很难让人信服 Castillo先生
See,I find that hard to believe,Mr.Castillo.
因为那个年轻小伙在你店里 买了Mariquitas苏打
After that young man bought this mariquitas soda from your store...
他走了出去 然后被人像一条狗一样杀死在街上
He walked out and got shot like a dog in the street.
他买了苏打后就离开店子了
He bought the soda. He left the store.
我听到了枪声 可是我什么都没有看到
I heard the shots,but-but I didn't see anything.
好吧 所以你是听到了枪声的
Okay,so you heard shots.
你没有往外看 没有看到一辆车离开?
You didn't look out,see a car take off?
拜托
Please...
- 别在这儿问 - 我理解
- Not here. - I understand.
要不你明天去警局就你看到的
Why don't you come down to the precinct tomorrow,give a statement?
录一份证词?
Just what you saw.
好 我明天去
Okay,I'll come down tomorrow.
Reese先生? 你去哪里了?
Mr.Reese? Where have you been?
我们有新号码了
We've got another number.
如果你要告诉我是Ronnie Middleton 那么你迟了点 Finch 这孩子已经死了
If you're gonna tell me ronnie middleton,you're a little late,finch.Kid's already gone.
什么? 你在哪里?
What? Where are you?
在凶杀现场 我在想为什么 机器能看到一些人却忽略了另一些人
At the scene of a homicide,wondering how the machine can see one and miss another.
我很抱歉 Reese先生 机器只能侦测到有预谋的行为
I'm sorry,Mr.Reese.The machine detects acts of premeditation.
这个机器现在看到的号码 我恐怕会是个大麻烦
And I'm afraid we've got a big problem with the one it's seeing right now.
谁的号码出来了?
Whose number came up?
我们共同的朋友...
Mutual friend of ours...
Carter警探
Detective carter.
Yi mean you've got like five chundred dollars worth of nuts here,you do the math.
要告诉我昨晚你在哪里么?
Want to tell me where you were last night?
我准备问你同样的问题
I was about to ask you the same thing.
忙活一件新案子
Working a new case.
- 这是你们要的 - 谢谢
- There you go. - Thank you.
我可没有宵禁
And I don't have the curfew.
我打电话时你不在家  你也不接手机 Taylor
You weren't home when I called,and you didn't answer your cell,taylor.
我只是迟了半小时
I was only a half an hour late.
我把这件案子了结前 你要跟奶奶呆在一起
Yeah. You're staying with grandma till I'm off this case.
嗨 Taylor
Hey,taylor.
放假返乡舞会周五开始 你要去吗?
So I saw you got that,uh,homecoming dance coming up friday.You gonna go?
是啊 新生一定不容易
Yeah,it must be tough being a freshman.
女孩们都和学长们约会去了
All the girls going out with the older guys.
- 我已经邀请人了 - 真的?
- I already asked somebody. - Really?
- 是的 - 那么 我想见见她
- Yeah. - Well,I want to meet her.
我上学要迟到了
I'm gonna be late for school.
我载你去 我有时间
I'm taking you.I have time.
坐下 我以为我充好电了
Stay. I thought I charged this thing.
**
- 你先 - 谢谢
- After you. - Thank you.
把你教得真好
Raised you well.
Carter 克隆电话 强制绑定完成
*****
你知道她有个儿子吗?
Did you know she had a son?
我不知道你还关心这个
Didn't know you cared.
没看见有爸爸
No dad in the picture for some time.
你有调查警探 Reese先生?
You been looking into the detective,Mr.Reese?
应该去了解追着你不放的人 Finch
It pays to know the person coming after you,finch.
他们现在要离开了
Okay,they're leaving now.
你最好快点
You'd better hurry up.
- 快好了 - 算了 快走
- Almost got it. - Forget it.Get out of there now.
我们有图像了吗?
Do we have picture?
***
还有一个GPS跟踪器 做得好 Harold
And a gps tracker. Nice work,harold.
我们得全天候看着她 即使她在警局也不例外
We need eyes and ears on her 24-7,even inside the precinct.
Finch Carter走向Hector的铺子里去了
Finch,carter's going right into hector's shop.
Ronnie Middleton枪杀案的首要嫌疑人
Primary suspect in the ronnie middleton shooting.
生意怎么样 Hector?
How's the car business,hector?
说的好像你真的关心似的 警探
You say that like you really care,detective.
我关心你昨晚在哪里
Care about where you were last night.
来吧 随便扯淡 来忽悠我吧
Go ahead,spin that yarn,dazzle me.
抱歉 我可是恋家的男人
Sorry. I'm a domesticated man.
我在家和我女人一起 看电视 问她
I was back with my old lady,watching some show.Ask her.
当然了 总是这种忠贞的不在场证明
Of course. Always with the loyal alibi.
你知道吗 Monica 他是挺帅 可你能找到更好的
You know,monica,he's handsome,but you can do better.
你敢一个人来这还真是有种 女士
you got some huevos coming down here all alone,lady.
那么说 昨晚在华盛顿高地 出现的不是你的肌肉车?
So that wasn't your muscle car took a detour into washington heights last night?
不 我听说那里很危险的
Nah,I hear it's dangerous down there.
我知道 你们都听说Ronnie Middleton的事了
I know y'all heard what happened to ronnie middleton.
我听说他吃了颗子弹 消化不良
I heard he ate a bullet that didn't agree with him.
不错的铺子 不错的工具
Nice shop,nice tools.
自己活得不错 Hector
Doing well for yourself,hector.
你修修旧车 就赚这么多钱?
You make all this money fixing up old cars?
我有前科 得为自己干活
I got a record. I got to work for myself.
这辆车不错 介意我看看吗?
This is a nice ride. You mind if I check it out?
当然介意了
Sure as hell do.
要看就拿搜查令来
You're gonna need a warrant for that.
你搞砸了 杀了那孩子 Hector
You messed up,taking that kid out,hector.
那孩子的事 我感到很惋惜...
It's a shame what happened to that kid...
即使他就是一告密小混混
Even if he was a punk-ass snitch.
这次你不会再逃脱了
You won't get away with it again.
我会找到办法定你罪
I will find a way to bring you down.
祝你有好运能拿到搜查令 警探
Good luck with that warrant,detective.
不知道你还收集娃娃啊 finch
Didn't know you collected dolls,finch.
你知道的 我收集绝版书 Reese先生
As you know,I collect rare books,Mr.Reese.
还有 180克黑胶唱片 施乐Alto电脑 如果我能找到的话
180-gram vinyl and a xerox alto when I can find one.
娃娃是给Fusco警探的
This doll is for detective fusco.
Fusco喜欢娃娃?
Fusco's into dolls?
如果我们想监视Carter警探的话 他现在就得开始喜欢了
He is now,if we want to keep eyes on detective carter.
我保证会送到他桌子上
I'll make sure it lands on his desk.
我详查了一下咱们的号码
I've been looking into our new number.
纽约警局任职记录
******
Carter 凶杀专案组一级警探
Carter,detective first grade,homicide task force.
单身母亲 一个十几岁的儿子 过去在部队里专门审讯犯人
Single mom,teenage son,served as an army interrogator.
2004年通过律师考试 但放弃做律师 回到军队
Passed the bar in '04,gave it up to go back on the force.
了不起啊 Reese先生
It's impressive,Mr.Reese.
了不起的女士 诚实得有点过分
Impressive lady.Honest to a fault.
那意味着 黑白两道她都得罪了很多人
Which means she made a lot of enemies,both in the criminal world and in her own department.
我把可能的嫌犯名单 缩小到了300个人左右
I've narrowed the list of possible suspects to a little over 300 or so.
凶杀案警探生活中普通的一天
Day in the life of a homicide detective.
有什么更紧迫的威胁吗?
Any more immediate threats?
Hector Alvarez... 是她6个月前的办的一个案子的嫌犯
Hector alvarez... Indicted for homicide on a case she worked six months ago...
但是控罪都撤销了
Till the charges were dropped.
Edward kovach 多次累犯 虐待妻子
Edward kovach - Repeat felon,spouse abuser,
她非常想保护他的妻子 然后就是 Elias
whose wife she's taken a keen interest in protecting.And then there's elias-
残忍的杀手 黑帮头子 已经试过杀她了
Ruthless killer,organized crime boss,who's already taken a shot at her.
她就是一活动靶子 一刻也不能让她离开视线
Well,she's a walking target.Gonna have to keep her in sight at all times.
你得小心点 太接近会有被抓的危险
You have to be careful.Get too close,you risk getting caught.
这个险我得冒
That's a chance I got to take.
不然我要怎么做 就由她吃枪子?
What am I supposed to do,let her catch a bullet?
要是她捉着你怎么办?
What will you do if she catches you?
我相信你会想办法的 Harold
Well,I'm sure you'll figure something out,harold.
*****
搞什么鬼?
What the hell?
Fusco警探
Detective fusco.
生日快乐 Lionel
Happy birthday,lionel.
谢谢 不用了
Thanks,but no thanks.
今天不是我生日 我不知道你到底目的何在
It's not my birthday.I don't know what the hell you're trying to tell me here.
你只要放在桌子上对着Carter就行了
Just put it on your desk and face it towards carter.
为什么?
Why?
因为里面装了摄像头 我们需要知道她都跟谁谈了话
'Cause there's a camera inside,and we need to know everyone she's talking to.
你知道我不知道的事?
You know something I don't?
- 她有麻烦了? - 你说呢
- She in trouble? - Well,you tell me.
跟你局里的黑警同胞们打听一下
Ask around with some of your corrupt pals inside the force.
嘿 怎么了? 你想要什么?
Hey,what's going on? What do you need?
我要查出是谁想要杀Carter
I need to find out who might want to take carter out.
哇哦 等等 我可不能扯进这种事里去
Whoa,wait a minute.I can't be involved in something like that.
不 Lionel 快把摄像头朝向她
No,lionel,just turn the camera towards her desk.
不错的娃娃
Nice doll.
嗯 我的 我的儿子送我的
Yeah,my,uh - My son gave it to me.
监狱里的老先生怎么了?
How'd it go with the old don at the big house?
想探探他 看他对自己的亲生儿子了解多少
Tried to reach out,see what he knew about his biological son.
- Elias哈? - 老头不睬我
Elias,huh? Old man just shut me down.
似乎是觉得所有警察都是坏的
Seems to think every cop is dirty.
嗯 也许他那会是这样子
Yeah. Maybe back in his day.
那个杂货店店主Castillo来了吗?
That bodega owner castillo come in yet?
据我所知没有
Not that I know of.
看来得再去找他
Gonna have to pay him another visit.
一起吗?
You coming?
不 要不 你自己去?
Nah,you know what?Why don't you,uh,go ahead?
我 我有点事 一会去找你 好吗?
I - I got a thing.I'll catch up with you later,okay?
好
Okay.
- 过来 - 嘿 我啥都没做
- Come here. - Yo,I ain't done nothing.
- 手放在我看得见的地方 - 放开
- Hands where I can see 'em. - Get off.
有针头吗? 有会刺伤我的东西吗?
Got any needles? Anything that's gonna stick me?
这是侵犯我的公民权利
This is violation of my civil liberties.
Finch 事情要不妙
Finch,I don't like the looks of this.
婊子 你最好放开我
Bitch,you better get your hands off me.
闭嘴 头低下
Shut up and get your head down.
感谢你把它搞得跟真的似的 警探
Yo,thanks for making it look good,detective.
我想我把手腕给拧了
I think I tweaked my wrist,man.
刚才有点太戏剧化了
That was a little too theatrical,bottlecap.
- 嘿 - 等等 Reese
- Hey- - Wait a minute,reese.
我想她认识他
I think she knows him.
刚才都是演戏 他一定是她的线人
It's all for show.Must be one of her c.i.s.
那是因为上次我被抓以后 我就花时间戒毒了
That's 'cause after I last got popped,I used my time to rehabilitate myself.
你戒毒了?
You got clean?
- 得了吧 B.C. - 我认真的 我身体里一点毒都没了
- Come on now,b.c. - I'm serious. These pipes are junk-free.
但我还是缺点钱 懂我意思吗?
But I can always use some scratch,you know what I'm saying?
我想知道关于一个 叫Elias的新人你都听到些什么
I need to know what you've heard about the new guy elias.
嗯 最近经常听到这名字
Yeah,I've been hearing that name up and coming a lot.
我没见过他 不过我听说 此人可不是闹着玩的
I never seen him,but I-I hear he's a man not to be trifled with.
昨晚168街和奥杜邦交界的枪杀案 听到些什么消息吗?
You,um,know anything about that shooting last night over on 168th and audubon?
驾车枪击 对吧?
Drive-by,right?
我知道那地方 但不知道谁干的
I know the block,just not the players.
你听过个叫Hector Alvarez的人吗 看到过他开着肌肉车在街区里晃吗?
You ever hear the name hector alvarez come up or see him cruise the block in his g.t.o.?
我没见过那车 也没听有人 谈起Hector 但我会去打听
I didn't see the car or hear nobody talk about hector,but I can ask around.
留神点 B.C.
Good looking out,b.c.
如果你有Hector或者Elias的消息 还会有更多钱
If you get anything back on,um,hector or elias,there's more where that came from.
嘿 队长
Hey,captain.
欢迎回来 警探
Welcome back,detective.
没想到你跟市区那些
Didn't think you'd grace us with your presence again
喷香水的人一起后还会赏脸回来
once you spent time with the perfumed folk downtown.
你这个笨蛋是怎么发达的?
How'd a half-wit like you pull that off?
我想我这笨蛋还是有一手的 嗯 队长?
I guess the half-wit's still got some juice,huh,captain?
他们让我和Carter警探搭档...
They got me working with detective carter,and...
我听到些传言
I'm starting to hear some things.
是嘛? 比如?
Yeah? Like what?
也许 呃 有些人不喜欢她
Maybe she's not so well-liked by,uh,a certain element.
听着 Lionel... 事情又恢复往昔了
Listen,lionel... Things are going back to the way they used to be.
- 往昔? - 黑帮那些事儿?
- Used to be? - Thing about organized crime?
有组织 管用
It was organized.Things worked.
一切守时有序
Trains ran on time.
这个新人... 他懂规矩
This new guy... He knows the rules.
新人 你是说Elias
New guy - You mean elias.
组织管理得很严密... 低调
Runs a tight ship... Low profile.
跟那些凶残的俄国白痴不一样
Not like these cutthroat russian idiots.
他知道要贿赂谁... 关节一直通到市政府里
He knows who to grease... All the way up to city hall.
听着 现在的经济情况就是一坨屎
Look,the economy's in the toilet.
Carter警探不懂游戏规则
Detective carter doesn't understand the rules.
她对生意不好
She's bad for business.
她做了什么?
What'd she do?
到处查探... 想要找证据
Sniffing around... Trying to build a case.
她枪头直指Elias 必须解决她
She's gunning for elias.She's got to go.
杀一个警察可不容易
It's a tricky business,getting rid of a cop.
通过合适的后门...  直接通过上面下命令
Went through the proper back channels... Up the chain of command.
已经授权了
Permission granted.
只需要做得... 干净
It's just got to look... Clean.
"干净"?  你是说弄得像殉职?
"Clean"? You mean like in the line of duty?
我开始觉得被夹在中间啊
I'm starting to feel caught in the middle here,captain.
如果我是你 就保持距离
I'd keep my distance,if I were you.
你没有去警局啊 你答应我的 Castillo先生
You didn't come down to the precinct like you told me you would,mr.Castillo.
今天我没帮手 我很忙
I got no help today. I'm a very busy man.
枪击发生前后 你有没有见过这辆车?
Did you see this car before or after the shooting?
你没跟我说那个被杀的 是另一件枪击案的目击者
You didn't tell me that the guy that they killed was a witness to another shooting.
他决定不出庭作证 但那没救他的命
He decided not to testify.Didn't save him.
如果你觉得这能说服我 那你错了
If you think that's gonna convince me to,it's not helping.
关键是... 如果Hector Alvarez 认为你看见他杀人
The point is... If hector alvarez thinks you saw him shoot someone,
他也会来杀你的
he's gonna come after you too.
求你了 听着 我有家人
Please.Look,I have a family.
对极了
Exactly.
如果你帮我 我会保护你和你的家人
If you help me,I can protect you and your family.
如果你不作证... 他还是会来杀你的
If you don't... He could still come after you.
怎么说 Lionel?
What's the word,lionel?
我四处打听了一下
I did some checking around.
Carter的名字冒出来 而且还不是好事
Carter's name came up and not in a good way.
Elias想她死... 今天
Elias wants her gone... Today.
杀警察太引人注意了
Killing a cop brings a lot of heat.
嗯 所以他们会做得很干净
Yeah,which is why they're gonna make it look clean.
他会找个替罪羊 或买通她正在查的案子里的人
He could set up a patsy or pay someone off on a case she's working.
我只知道 Carter时刻有被杀的危险
All I know is,every door that carter walks through could have a bullet behind it.
昨晚这人来你店里了吗?
Did you see this guy in your store last night?
拜托 我只需要知道这个
Please. That's all I need.
我之前见过他
I saw him earlier.
以前他来买过保险套 啤酒
He's been in my store before,to buy condoms,beer.
有什么关系?  反正我不会给你作证
What does it mater? I'm not gonna give you a statement anyways.
可以请你离开我的店吗?
Can you please leave my store?
好吧 好吧 谢谢
Okay. Okay. Thank you.
哦 对不起 警探
Oh,sorry,detective.
我从后面没认出是你来
I didn't realize that was you from behind.
如今外面太多美女了
Lot of fine girls out today.
走开 情圣
Keep it moving,lover boy.
在这个街区你可得小心
You got to be careful on this block.
我听说昨晚有个小孩被杀了
I heard some kid got popped last night.
你有孩子吗 警探?
You got any kids,detective?
离这个街区远点
Stay off this block.
我再看见这车经过这里一次 我就会扣押它
I see this car roll by one more time,i'm gonna impound it.
回头见 Castillo先生
I'll be seeing you around,mr.Castillo.
- 快滚 - 我们走
- Get out of here. - Let's go.
Elias要除掉Carter
Elias wants carter gone.
可能会利用有杀她动机的人... 她手上的嫌疑犯
Possible he'll use someone with motive... The suspect in one of her cases.
Carter在酒吧
Carter's at a bar.
我以为她在工作呢
I thought she was on duty.
有这么多人想找她麻烦 我都想请她喝一杯
With this many people after her,i'd be inclined to pick up the tab.
说说看 Eddie...
Tell me,eddie...
哪种混蛋会把老婆打成这样?
What kind of degenerate es that to his wife?
Carter去见Kovach了
Carter's paying kovach a visit.
负责谋杀案的警官怎么还管家务事?
Why is a homicide detective intervening in a domestic case?
也许她跟我们一样 想阻止不好的事情发生
Maybe she's like us.Trying to prevent something bad from happening.
夫妻之间的家务事关你屁事
What happens between a man and his woman behind closed doors is none of your damn business.
你喝死了我都不管
Can't stop you from boozing your life away.
但你要是回家再对老婆动手 我不会放过你
But you go home and put your hands on your wife again,i'm coming after you.
你要是来干涉 休怪我枪杆子伺候
You come after me,and I will exercise my second amendment rights.
我告诉你 我那把枪可大
And I promise you,I got a pretty big gun.
像你这种狂暴恶毒的人...
Man as angry and bitter as you are...
枪 Gun: 美俚中有男性生殖器的意思
I got a feeling it ain't that big,eddie.
我觉着你那把"枪"不会很大 Eddie
不得不承认 Finch 我喜欢她这范儿
I got to admit,finch,I sure like her style.
我想我们有领头羊了
I think we got a new front-runner.
Mark Thomson
Mark thomson,
Ricky Lopez
ricky lopez,
Joseph Mcnally...
joseph mcnally...
都死于你帮忙运送的自杀炸弹背心
All were killed from a suicide vest you helped transport.
他们有家庭... 有爱他们的人
They had families... People that loved them.
我为士兵们感到惋惜 但我运的是蔬菜
I'm sorry for the soldiers,but I deliver vegetables.
我知道你为基地组织卖命 Yusuf...
I know you're working with al-qaeda,yusuf...
因为我有你装货的照片
'cause I have photos here of you loading vests into your truck.
你想说这些照片都是假的吗?
Now,you want to tell me all these photos of you are fake?
告诉我其他自杀炸弹藏在哪儿 Yusuf
Show me where the other suicide vests are hidden,yusuf.
指出来
Point to the location.
你知道要是他们知道 我帮了你会怎么对我吗?
Do you know what they will do if they find out that I helped you?
会杀了我妻子
They will kill my wife.
杀了我儿子
They will kill my son.
还不如你现在杀了我呢
I would rather you just kill me now.
Carter 是我们赶到时已经死了的 那个 Ronnie Middleton的手机吗?
Carter,is that the d.o.a.'s phone - Ronnie middleton?
她妈妈还没去太平间
His mother hasn't even come to the morgue.
这孩子一直是一个人
This kid was all alone.
他不该这么惨
He deserved better.
到现在还没找到一点 有关Hector的线索
So far,I've got nothing on hector.
即时犯罪打击中心的分析员
Analyst from the real-time crime center sent over footage
把Nueva杂货店附近 一些摄像头的录像发了过来
from some of the cameras around bodega la nueva.
**
一些? 还不止这些摄像头吗?
Some? There's more cameras than this?
是的 市长希望每个角落都装上
Yeah. Mayor wants one on every corner.
怪不得我总觉得有人看着我
Wow,no wonder I feel like I'm always being watched.
我觉得Hector那辆肌肉车 应该经过这个路口 但什么都没有
I figured hector's g.t.o.Had to pass through this intersection,but nothing,nada.
也许他没开车 走过去的
Maybe he didn't drive. Maybe he walked.
Castillo说 他去过店里几次 买酒和避孕套
Castillo said he came into his market a couple times to purchase some booze and trojans.
- 然后呢? - 他女朋友也住在布朗克斯区
- So? - His girlfriend lives in the bronx too.
买个避孕套 干嘛要走25个街区?
Why would he have to go 25 blocks downtown for condoms?
因为唐璜(莫里哀笔下的花心流氓) 还有个小情人
'Cause don juan got a little chicky on the side..
Hector是走过去的
Hector was on foot.
也许他从她公寓走到店里
Maybe he walked from her apartment to the market.
在那儿撞见的Ronnie
And that's where hector bumped into ronnie.
如果能找到这个小情人 也许能找到新的证人
if we can find this chica,we might have ourselves a new witness.
我打几个电话
I'm gonna make some phone calls.
我得走了 回头再谢我吧?
Look,I got to go.You can thank me later,all right?
这么快又想我了?
Hello.What,do you miss me already?
这个比较困难 Lionel
You're a hard man to miss,lionel.
只能说Carter的情况让你担心了
I'd say this carter situation's got you worried.
你准备怎么办 从现在开始跟着她?
What are you gonna do,follow her around from now on?
不是我跟 你去跟
I'm not. You are.
我还有些事要做
I've got some business to take care of.
别让她惹上麻烦
Don't let her get in any trouble.
Carter在追查你
Carter's gunning for you.
靠 她也许会抓到你
Hell,she's probably gonna catch you.
你干嘛费这么大力气保护她?
Why you spending so much time trying to protect her?
她是个好警察... 好人
She's a good cop... Good person.
靠 你有空该学着点 Lionel
Hell,you should try it sometime,lionel.
好吧 谢了 听着 我是说 如果她不在这儿
Yeah,thanks,look,I'm just saying,if she wasn't around,
能省你不少事 不是吗?
it would probably solve a lot of your problems,now,wouldn't it?
如果她出了事 我接着就找你算账
If anything happens to her,lionel,i'm coming for you next.
搞什么...
What the-
敲门 敲门
Knock,knock.
有些什么呀?
What do we have here?
Hector真是大忙人 又修车又卖枪
Hector's a busy man - Fixing cars and running guns.
你谁啊?
Who are you,man?
告诉Hector 我是砸他铺子的人
Tell hector I'm the guy that just put him out of business.
如果我再看到他 砸的就不止是铺子了
If I see him again,I'll close down more than the shop.
如果你帮我们 我能保护你和你的家人
If you help us,I can protect you and your family.
我保证
I promise.
对你来说这只是个谈判
This is just a negotiation for you.
你根本不关心我和我的家人
You don't care about me or my family.
你的儿子 跟你一个名字
Your son - He's named after you.
还有14天就8岁了吧?
He's turning 8 in 14 days,right?
最喜欢的运动是? 足球
Favorite sport? Soccer.
但因为你 他踢足球太危险
But it's too dangerous to play in the field by you.
你唯一的哥哥 Naji 9个月前被简易炸弹炸死
Your only brother,naji,was killed nine months ago by an i.e.d.
你每天去墓地看他
You visit his grave every day.
你看... 这不仅仅是谈判...
So,you see... You are not just a negotiation...
对我而言不是
Not to me.
- 你有孩子吗? - 有一个儿子 叫Taylor
- Do you have children? - A son. Taylor.
你会把他的命托付给陌生人吗?
Would you trust his life to a complete stranger?
我会竭尽所能保护他
I'd do whatever was in my power to protect him.
你失去了哥哥 Yusuf
You lost your brother,yusuf.
我也失去了一个非常亲近的人
I lost someone very close to me too.
改变了一切
It changed everything.
你和我... 其实没什么两样
You and me... We're not that different.
没错 我们有共同的愿望
no. We want the same thing.
希望孩子走在路上不用担心受怕
For our children to walk down the street and not be afraid.
告诉我炸弹在哪儿
Show me where those explosives are.
地图上没有的
The location is not on the map.
那你带我们去
Then you'll take us to them.
为了我们的孩子
For our children.
B.C. 有Hector新欢的消息吗?
Hey,b.c. You got anything on hector's new woman?
放松 Fusco没关系的
Relax. Fusco's all right.
放松 好小子 我不咬人
Easy there,hubcap.I don't bite.
好吧 我直说了
All right,let's make this quick.
我看见Hector的肌肉车 停在Lookie-loo门口
I seen hector's g.t.o. Outside the lookie-loo.
他搭上了里面跳舞的 叫Mei Li
Turns out he's bumping one of the dancers-mel li.
要我说 Hector喜新厌旧了
If you ask ask me,hector got a little tired of his chica and wanted some strange.
干得好
You done good.
我以为你说...  你给我大钱... 奖金呢
I thought you said... You know,real money... Reward money.
行啊 等这案子结了 我给奖金
Okay. Well,if this pans out,I will get you that reward money.
回头见 请你在你最爱的餐厅吃饭
I'll meet you later,even take you to dinner at your favorite spot.
好啊 因为是你请我 我才会去
All right. Yeah,but only 'cause it's you.
你总是对我很好 Carter
You always been good to me,carter.
好 保重
Okay. Take care.
对 我和Hector一晚都在一起
Yes,me and hector was together all night.
看电视 然后上床
We watched tv,and then we went to bed.
看了什么?
What'd you watch?
我不知道 Hector一直在换台
I don't know.Hector's always changing the channels.
我听说他是这样
I heard that about that guy.
很容易厌倦 总是换来换去的吧?
He gets bored,he likes to switch it up,huh?
所以他才勾搭别的姑娘?
Is that why he has that other girl on the side?
不 不 不 我的男人不会背叛我的
No,no,no. You see,my man don't step out on me.
我会解决掉的
I'll cut it off.
好吧 来 给你看样东西
Ooh,okay. Come here.I want you to see something.
这是Hector的电话单
That's hector's cell phone bill.
你知道这是谁的电话? 他拨了33次
You know whose number that is? 'cause he dialed it 33 times.
我不知道 可能是手下的人
I don't know,it's probably one of his homies.
那男人八卦起来跟女学生似的
That man gossips like a little schoolgirl.
要知道很简单
Well,it's easy enough to find out.
来 拨一个
Go ahead. Dial it.
你跟Hector一整晚都在一起
So you were with hector all night.
昨天晚上和今天早上
Last night,this morning.
Hector早上特精神 喜欢爱抚
Hector's a morning person.He likes to spoon.
喂?
hello?
- 喂? - 谁啊?
- Hello? - Who is this?
等等 你他妈的是谁?
Wait. Who the hell are you?
好吧 看起来你们俩有很多问题要解决
Okay,all right.Looks like you two got a lot to sort out.
别让她们干了对方
make sure they don't kill each other.
- 不! - 不! 开什么玩笑!
- Oh,no! - Oh,no!You got to be kidding me!
Carter 看来跟Hector Alvarez 干上的不只有你
Carter,looks like you're not the only one who's got a beef with hector alvarez.
有人今天冲进他店里 横扫一通
Some guy came into his body shop and shot up the place.
里面那帮人自食其果
Bangers inside got a taste of their own medicines.
听说那人有冲锋枪和手榴弹发射器
Said the guy had a submachine gun and a grenade launcher.
你信吗?
You believe that?
那人穿西装的吗?
This guy wearing a suit?
不是 是机车夹克 怎么了?
No,motorcycle jacket.why?
也许送去干洗了
Maybe it's in the cleaners.
Hector被传讯 但是他不见了
Hector's wanted for questioning.Suffice it to say,he's,uh,disappeared.
有人知道他在哪儿
Somebody knows where he is.
如果我找到Hector 我得好好审
If I find hector,i'll give him your best.
Hector开溜了
Hector's on the run.
他不会再对Carter构成威胁了
He's not gonna be a problem for carter anymore.
这可不一定
I'm not so sure about that.
Carter现在一心为Ronnie讨公道
Carter is now determined to get justice for ronnie.
无论如何 她都会找到Hector的藏身之所
One way or another,she will find where hector's hiding.
那家伙卖枪的
The guy's running guns.
不管藏在哪儿 都全副武装
Wherever he is,he's heavily armed.
- 等她去逮捕他... - 我得先到那里
- And when she goes to arrest him- - I'll just have to get there first.
你没事吧 Reese先生?
Is everything okay,mr.Reese?
我们干这个 为了保护好人不受伤害
We got into this to stop bad things from happening to good people.
Carter一辈子都在干这个
Carter's been doing that her whole life.
她不仅仅是又一个数字 Finch
She's not just another number,finch.
是这世界不能失去的人
Some people the world can't afford to lose.
有人愿意做供了吗?
Either one of you ready to make a statement?
我来说
Yeah,I got a statement.
如果Hector Alvarez以为能耍我们 他就是一傻逼
Hector alvarez is a damn fool if he thinks he can play us both.
那混蛋那天去了我那儿 但半夜走了
Bastard came to my place,but he went out around midnight.
他去买东西了?
Did he go to the market?
他是那么说 但他空手回来还换了衣服
What he said.But he came back empty-handed and changed his shirt.
你给他洗了?
You wash this shirt of his?
鬼才给他洗 都归你了 连同他别的东西
Oh,hell,no. It's all yours along with all his stuff.
Hector在哪儿?
So where is hector?
他在皇后区有个仓库... 25街
He has a warehouse in queens... On 25th.
他等货来的时候就在那附近混
He hangs out there sometimes when he's expecting a shipment.
让紧急防暴队出一队特警候着
Call e.s.u.,get a team on standby.
我去拿逮捕令
I'm gonna see about getting a warrant.
- 喂? - 他有枪
- Hello? - He's got a gun!
等等 冷静点 我听不清楚
Uh,wait a minute.Calm down. I can't understand you.
- 他有枪 - 滚出来!
- He's got a gun! - Get out of there!
天啊! 救命! 他要杀了我! 快来!
Oh,god! Please! He's gonna kill me! Hurry!
Kovach太太 你在哪儿?
Mrs.Kovach,where are you?
- 浴室! - 呆在原地 我过去找你
- In the bathroom! - Stay where you are.I'm gonna come and get you.
喂? 喂?
Hello? Hello?
Carter要去Kovachs的住所
Carter's going to the kovachs' house.
他有武器 听上去气坏了
He's armed,sounds extremely agitated.
Reese? 你在哪里?
Reese? Where are you?
各单位 枪击事件
All units,we have a code ten.
地点法拉盛绿树街326号
Shots fired at 326 greentree in flushing.
纽约警察 开门!
N.y.p.d.,open up!
确定我们不等后援了? 我有点不良预感
Sure we shouldn't wait for backup? I got a bad feeling about this.
Kovach先生... 警察 放下武器
Mr.Kovach... It's the police.Put down your weapon.
搞什么?
What the hell?
有人把他包好了当礼物送我们了
Somebody gif wrapped him for us.
有人最近干了不少这样的事
Somebody's been doing that a lot lately.
Kovach太太? Kovach太太?
Mrs.Kovach? Mrs.Kovach?
Kovach太太 你还好么?
Mrs.Kovach,are you okay?
他会杀了我的
He was gonna kill me.
要不是那人来了...
If that man hadn't shown up-
"那人"? 他长什么样?
"That man"? What'd he look like?
喂?
Hello?
找你的
It's for you.
我想我得为此对你表示感谢
I guess I have you to thank for this.
你怎么总知道坏事啥时发生?
How do you always know when something bad's about to go down?
你有危险 警探
You're in trouble,detective.
我不是那个东躲西藏的人
I'm not the one who's hiding.
听好 你再这么自以为上帝掌管生杀 迟早会有无辜的人因此受伤
Look,you keep playing god,and sooner or later,an innocent person's gonna get hurt.
我不能由你胡来
I can't let that happen.
你听好 我打来不是谈我的事
Listen,I didn't call to talk about me.
你有生命危险
Your life's in danger.
我是警察 我经常有生命危险
I'm a cop.My life's always in dange
你没在听我说 我意思是有人要杀你
You're not listening to me.I'm trying to tell you someone wants you dead.
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
你跟着我做什么? 你想要什么?
Why are you following me?What do you want?
我想要你小心行事
I want you to start being more careful.
比如说 你想拿下Hector Alvarez
For instance,if you're gonna take down hector alvarez,
你得知道他卖军火的
you should know the man's running guns.
他的军火库随手可及
He has an arsenal at his fingertips.
你为什么要帮我?
What-why are you helping me?
你如何得知这些信息的?
And how do you keep finding out all of this information?
像你说的... 我一直都知道
Like you said... I always seem to know.
我没看见他的脸 他突然冒出来
I never saw his face.He came out of nowhere.
袭击了我
He attacked me.
你们不能逮捕我
You people can't arrest me.
我们可以 你妻子提出控诉了 Eddie
Yes,we can. Your wife is pressing charges,eddie.
拿到对Hector Alvarez的逮捕令了吗?
We get a warrant on hector alvarez yet?
嗯 防暴警已经就位 谁死了?
Yep,e.s.u.'s standing by.Who died?
深切哀悼Carter警探
****
Finch Carter让一队防暴警去 Hector皇后区的仓库了
Finch,carter's called an e.s.u.Unit to hector's warehouse in queens.
我们说话这会儿 他们已经上门了
They're getting ready to knock on the door as we speak.
该行动了
It's time to roll.
留在原地 我们抓到Alvarez后通知你
Stay here. I'll advise you when we have alvarez apprehended.
你能看到Carter吗?
You have eyes on carter?
她在火线以外
She's clear of the line of fire.
如果Hector反击 她可能有危险
If hector puts up a fight,it could be dangerous.
你能到她近前保护她吗?
How will you be close enough to protect her?
我... 很近了
Oh,I'm... Pretty close.
- 这地方各出口都守住了 对吧? - 当然
- They got this place covered,right? - Absolutely.
- 要进去了 各就各位? - 准备好了 长官
- Cover's going in.Everybody set? - Yes,sir.
开门
Open it.
进去
Do it.
上! 上! 上! 纽约警察!
Move! Move! Move!N.y.p.d.!
趴地上!
Down on the ground now!
听起来不妙
That doesn't sound good.
你听见后面有动静了没?
You hear something around back?
下车
Get out of the car.
- 疑犯抓获 - 轻点
- Suspect apprehended. - Take it easy.
一切安好吗 Reese先生?
Everything all right,mr.Reese?
Hector有了一副新手环
Hector's got a new set of bracelets.
他应该有一阵子忙了
Should keep him busy for a while.
这是为了Ronnie
That's for ronnie.
我说过我会抓着你的
I told you I'd get you.
天啊 疼
Oh,god.
Taylor 亲爱的 我有点晚了 很快到
Y,taylor,baby.I'm running a little late. I'll be there soon.
Carter要回家了
Sounds like carter's headed home.
熬过今天了
Made it through the day.
我们解除威胁了没有?
Have we eliminated the threat yet?
来自Kovach和Alvarez的解除了
Kovach and alvarez are neutralized.
但这次情况不同寻常
But this is a tricky case.
说实话 我... 不确定
To be perfectly honest,i'm just... Not sure.
Finch Carter住在上城区
Finch,carter lives uptown.
她往下城区去干什么?
So why is she headed downtown?
等一下
Wait a minute.
她去哪儿了?
Where'd she go?
我跟丢了
I lost her.
追踪她的电话
Track her phone for me.
你去哪儿了? 你说了请我吃饭的
Where you been? You said you was gonna buy me dinner.
你上哪儿去了? 我一直等着呢
Where you been? I been waiting.
抱歉 B.C. 我得填表申请奖金
I'm sorry,b.c.I got to fill out a requisition for the big payout.
你先从我这儿拿点凑数吧?
But look,why don't you take whatever I got?
没关系 你不用给我
No,that's all right.You ain't got to do all that.
就当是预付款好么? 我希望你拿着
Let's just call this a down payment,okay? I want you to have that.
抱歉 Carter
I'm sorry,carter.
你一直对我不薄 但我别无选择
You always been good to me,but I ain't got no choice.
你让我找那Elias
You told me to find that guy elias.
我找到他了
Well,I found him.
对不起
Sorry.
他说要么你死 要么我死
He said it's either gonna be you or me.
我不想死
And it ain't gonna be me.
精神不错 Carter
Look alive,carter.
你那朋友带我去那地方找到的
About all that's left of that storage facility your friend took us to.
你找到炸药了
You found the explosives.
找到了 安全引爆了
Found and detonated.
我就办不到你办成的事 从中东佬嘴里撬信息什么的
I,uh,couldn't have done what you did,getting information from that raghead.
Yusuf在哪儿?
Where's yusuf?
他啊... 回不来了
Yeah,he,uh... Didn't make it back.
总会出意外嘛
Accidents happen.
他信任我
He trusted me.
我向他承诺
I gave him my word.
我承诺要保护他
I - I promised I'd protect him.
你不该承诺你办不到的事
You shouldn't make promises you can't keep.
拜托 你以为这家伙无辜?
Come on,you don't think this guy was innocent,do you?
他有家人
He had a family.
你不关心他们会怎么样吗?
Don't you care what happens to them?
我的工作又不是关心别人
It's not my job to care.
你什么毛病?
What is wrong with you?
你不能把自己当上帝!
You can't just play god!
你不能决定他人的生死!
You don't get to decide who lives and who dies!
你想占领道德制高点随你便
You want to stand on your high horse,go ahead.
但别指望我和我的人会当你后盾
But don't expect me and my men to back you up.
战事漫长
It's a long war.
只你孤身一人
And you're all alone.
幸好你接受我的建议穿了防弹衣
Glad you took my advice about wearing that vest,detective.
我知道这改变不了什么
I know this doesn't change anything.
我知道一有机会你还会逮捕我
I know you'll still arrest me if you get the chance.
但你应该知道 不管你喜不喜欢我 Joss
But you should know,whether you like me or not,joss,
你不是孤身一人
you're not alone.
Elias收买了Carter的线人
Elias got to carter's c.i.
找他当杀手
Turned him into his triggerman.
- 她安全了吗? - 暂时是
- Is she safe? - For now.
该结束了 Finch 一了百了
Time to end this,finch,once and for all.
这么高摔下去 可是死无全尸 一塌糊涂
Body falls from this height,it's messy.
当然 我可不会关心什么干不干净...
Of course,I don't care about making it look clean...
不像你朋友Elias
Unlike your pal elias.
我不认识你 但你在威胁一个警队队长
I don't know who you are,but you're threatening a captain.
好吧 好吧
Okay,okay,okay.
Elias没有批准不会杀警察
Elias can't kill a cop without permission.
传话给指挥链
Run this up the chain of command.
批准被驳回
Permission's been revoked.
告诉Elias他敢再碰Carter警探
Tell elias if he so much as touches detective carter again,
我会让他 让你 让所有人都下地狱
I will put him,you...Everyone in the ground.
- 明白了? - 明白
- You got that? - Yeah.
外婆说你又过了规定时间才回家
Grandma said you were late for curfew again.
拜托 妈 你来真的?
Oh,come on,ma.You're serious?
我去参加舞会了
I was at a dance.
她漂亮不?
Is she pretty?
最好还得聪明
Better be smart too.
又聪明又漂亮
Smart and pretty.
你还好吗 妈妈? 你伤着背了?
You all right,mom? Did you pull your back or something?
不是什么治不好的毛病
It's nothing that won't heal.
抱歉我错过了
Sorry I missed it,t.
你干活太累了 你应该辞职
You work too hard.You should quit.
就算想辞我也不知道怎么辞
Wouldn't know how to if I tried.
我不喜欢 你每天在外面
I don't like it - You out there every day.
谁能保护你呢?
Who's got your back?
你不用担心我
You don't have to worry about me.
我能照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
再说了... 我们互相照应
Besides... We got each other.
要别人干什么?
Who else do we need?
疑犯追踪 第1季 第9集
Person of Interest S01E09 720p HDTV x264
伊甸园字幕